adultcentro.com 2019-02-07

# AdultCentro | About Us - (AC)

Thank you for visiting the AdultCentro™ website located at [www.adultcentro.com](http://adultcentro.com/) (the "Site"). The Site is an Internet property of Content Centro Ltd ("AdultCentro™," "we" or "us"). AdultCentro™ is committed to protecting the privacy of our visitors’ personal and/or business information. We provide this AdultCentro™ Privacy Policy ("Privacy Policy") in order to explain our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is used by us. You agree to this Privacy Policy, in its entirety, when you: (a) access or use the Site; and/or (b) submit an application to become a member of the Site (“Member”), which enables you to access the AdultCentro™ proprietary exchange platform (the “AdultCentro™ Publisher”), as well as various products and/or services offered by AdultCentro™ through the AdultCentro™ Publisher (collectively, and as further described below, the “AdultCentro™ Services”). If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy in its entirety, you are not authorized to use the Site, AdultCentro™ Publisher and/or AdultCentro™ Services in any manner or form whatsoever.

**Personal/Entity Information**

We collect personal and business information when individuals, acting in their capacity as authorized representatives of legal business entities or legal partnerships (each, an "Entity"), register to become Members of the Site, or otherwise choose to provide personal or business information to us. Personal/ Entity information is any information that can be used to identify or locate a particular person or Entity. The personal/ Entity information that you provide to us may include, but is not limited to, your: (a) full name; (b) e-mail address; (c) role with the applicable Entity; as well as the applicable Entity’s: (d) legal name; (e) business structure; (f) primary business activity; (g) mailing address; (h) telephone number; (i) fax number; (j) general e-mail address; (k) website address; and/or (l) any and all other information requested on the applicable registration form. **We may also collect your personal/Entity information when you otherwise agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy, but do not complete the applicable registration process in full.**

**Non-Personal Information and Cookies**

We may collect certain non-personally identifiable information about you and/or your Entity when you visit many of the Site’s pages, such as the type of browser you are using (e.g., Netscape, Internet Explorer), the type of operating system you are using, (e.g., Windows 7 or Mac OS) and the domain name of your Internet service provider (e.g., NetZero, Earthlink). We use the non-personally identifiable information that we collect to improve the design and content of the Site, AdultCentro™ Publisher and/or AdultCentro™ Services, and to enable us to personalize your Internet experience. We also may use this information in the aggregate to analyze Site and/or AdultCentro™ Publisher usage.

The Site uses technology called "cookies". A cookie is a tiny element of data that the Site can send to your browser, which may then be stored on your hard drive so that we can recognize you when you return. Cookies also allow us to store Site users’ preferences and to record session information. We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personal information that you submit while on the Site. You may be able to configure your browser to accept or reject all or some cookies, or notify you when a cookie is set -- each browser is different, so check the applicable "Help" menu of your browser to learn how to change your cookie preferences. If you set your browser not to accept cookies, you will still be able to use the Site. The Site may also use technology called “tracer tags.” These may also be referred to as “Clear GIFs” or “Web Beacons.” This technology allows us to understand which pages you visit on the Site. These tracer tags are used to help us optimize and tailor the Site, AdultCentro™ Publisher and/or AdultCentro™ Services for you and other future Site visitors. To find out more about cookies, please visit [www.cookiecentral.com](http://cookiecentral.com/).

**Use of Personal/Entity Information**

We use your personal/Entity information to facilitate your use of the Site, and in order to facilitate your use of the AdultCentro™ Publisher and/or AdultCentro™ Services. We also use your personal/Entity information to send you information about AdultCentro™, our products and/or services and certain third party products and/or services that we think may be of interest to you. In connection with this, we use your personal information to provide marketing messages to you by means of e-mail advertising, telemarketing, direct mail marketing, pop-ups, pop-unders and/or online banner advertising.

Without limiting the foregoing, by submitting your telephone number at the Site, you agree that such act constitutes a purchase, an inquiry and/or an application for purposes of the Amended Telemarketing Sales Rule, 16 CFR §310 et seq. (the "ATSR"). With respect to the ATSR, and notwithstanding that your telephone number may be listed on the Federal Trade Commission’s Do-Not-Call List, AdultCentro™ retains the right to contact you via telemarketing in accordance with the terms of the ATSR.

**Information Sharing**

As a general rule, and other than in connection with the limited exceptions set forth below, AdultCentro™ will not sell, share or rent your personal/Entity information to or with others. Notwithstanding the foregoing, AdultCentro™ may, from time to time, provide such information on a limited basis to certain third-party administrative service providers in connection with: (a) your use of the AdultCentro™ Services; (b) your use of the AdultCentro™ Publisher; and/or (c) AdultCentro’s™ efforts to market certain offers to you. Any third-party so used has agreed to protect the confidentiality of information provided by AdultCentro™.

Further, AdultCentro™ reserves the right to share your personal/Entity information: (i) where required by law, or requested by a court of competent jurisdiction; (ii) in the event that AdultCentro™ is sold or acquired; (iii) where you are in violation of this Privacy Policy and/or the AdultCentro™ Website Terms and Conditions; or (iv) where AdultCentro™ determines, in its sole discretion, that such disclosure is necessary to protect the rights of AdultCentro™ and/or a third party, or necessary to protect AdultCentro™ from liability of any kind. The aforementioned includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection purposes.

**Use of Non-Personal Information**

AdultCentro™ reserves the right to transfer and/or sell aggregate or group data about Site users for lawful purposes. Aggregate or group data is data that describes the demographics, usage or other characteristics of Site users as a group without disclosing personally identifiable information. Subject to applicable state and federal law, by submitting your personal/Entity information to us, and/or using the Site, you agree to allow AdultCentro™ to transfer and/or sell aggregate data to third-parties.

**Third Party Websites**

The Site may contain links to other third-party owned and/or operated websites. AdultCentro™ is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites. In some cases, you may be able to make a purchase through one of their third-party websites. In these instances, you may be required to provide certain information, such as a credit card number, to register or complete a transaction at such website. These third-party websites have separate privacy and data collection practices and AdultCentro™ has no responsibility or liability relating to them.

**Minors**

We encourage parents and guardians to spend time online with their children and to participate and monitor the interactive activities of their children. AdultCentro™ will never knowingly directly collect any information from individuals under eighteen (18) years of age. If AdultCentro™ obtains actual knowledge that it has collected information from an individual under eighteen (18) years of age, that information will be immediately deleted from our database.

**Security**

All collected information is stored in a technically and physically secure environment. While we strive to protect your personal/Entity information, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information that you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your personal/Entity information, we make reasonable efforts to ensure its security on our systems.

Access to personal information is strictly limited, and not accessible to the public. All of our visitors’ personal information is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job function are granted access to personal information. Our employees are dedicated to ensuring the security and privacy of all visitors’ personal information. Employees not adhering to our written firm policies are subject to disciplinary action. In compliance with applicable federal and state laws, we shall notify you and any applicable regulatory agencies in the event that we learn of an information security breach with respect to your personal information. You will be notified via e-mail in the event of such a breach. Please be advised that notice may be delayed in order to address the needs of law enforcement, determine the scope of network damage, and to engage in remedial measures.

**Deleting and Updating Your Information**

If you would like to delete or update the personal/Entity information that we have collected from you, send your request via email to: [support@adultcentro.com](mailto:support@adultcentro.com). We will process your request, where possible and subject to the terms and conditions contained herein, within a reasonable period of time after receipt. To protect your privacy and security, we will take reasonable steps to help verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.

**Opting Out of Receiving Marketing Messages**

You may at any time choose to stop receiving e-mail advertising, telemarketing or direct mail marketing from us by following the instructions at the end of the applicable marketing message or by contacting us at: [support@adultcentro.com](mailto:support@adultcentro.com). Notwithstanding the foregoing, we may continue to contact you for the purpose of communicating information relating to your use of the AdultCentro™ Publisher and/or AdultCentro™ Services, general information regarding AdultCentro™, as well as to respond to any inquiry or request made by you.

**Notification of Changes**

If we change our Privacy Policy, we will prominently post a link to those changes on the Site’s homepage so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use personal/Entity information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify the affected Site users by way of an e-mail communication. Your continued use of the Site and/or continued receipt of AdultCentro™ Publishering messages after posting of the Privacy Policy change on the Site, or receipt of a Privacy Policy change notification e-mail, as applicable, constitutes an affirmative acknowledgement and acceptance by you of the modified Privacy Policy.

**Contact Us**

If you have any questions regarding this Privacy Policy, or would like more information on our privacy practices, please email us at: [support@adultcentro.com](mailto:support@adultcentro.com)

**Filing a Complaint with the Federal Trade Commission**

To file a complaint regarding our privacy practices, please [Click Here](https://www.ftccomplaintassistant.gov/FTC_Wizard.aspx?Lang=en).
